[
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 1+1",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 2+2",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 3+3",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 4+4",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 5+5",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 6+6",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 7+7",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 8+8",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 9+9",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 20+20",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 24+24",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 35+35",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 80+10",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 52+52",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 521+251",
        "answer": 772
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 125+11",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 10+12",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 51+51",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 14+14",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 12+521",
        "answer": 533
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 41+16",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 25+26",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "WHAT IS 14+125",
        "answer": 139
    }
]